this exercise is similar to the previous
one
however this time we want to alter our
code
so that we only print out values that
are greater than
five so in this case we want to output
only 6 through 10
instead of 1 through 10. we can do this
with a simple if statement
so inside of the block
we'll write an if statement and the
condition that we need to provide our if
statement in this case
is number is greater than 5.
this comparison is going to return
either true or false
if it returns true line 5 will be
executed
and we'll output the number otherwise
there will be no output so we can run
our code and see this
and we see that only 6 7 8 9 and 10
the numbers greater than 5 have been
output
this block can also be written on one
line
and let's see an example of that
rather than writing a multi-line if
statement
we can use if as a statement modifier
so we want to output number if
number is greater than five
and we'll run our code to see the same
behavior